DENNIS-IMMANUEL CZOGALLA | Resume

https://github.com/denczo • # www.pygineer.info

SUMMARY

Curious and highly motivated full stack developer with 5+ years experience in the industry. Proficient with React, Javascript and Typescript. Excels at problem-solving, creative thinking and teamwork skills which allows to deliver suitable solutions within a given deadline. Seeking to become a valuable member of the team and to contribute to the success of the company.

Experience _____

CREATIVE TECHNOLOGIST 01/2021 - 05/2023

Vivents GmbH

Heidelberg, Germany

- collaborated with an interdisciplinary team to develope an online platform to host and manage virtual events with 300+ user
- improved the reliability and stability of the platform's chat by refactoring existing components and implemented new features to improve the user experience (ReactJS, Typescript, GraphQL, Sass, Redux)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER 09/2019 - 12/2020

German Cancer Research Center

Heidelberg, Germany

- collaborated with two Scrum-Teams to develope software which support doctors in the planning of cancer treatment and to collect medical data of volunteer participants for scientific research
- transformed medical data of 200k patients for further analysis (JAVA, Maven, JDBC, SQL)
- setup of an database infrastructure for faster data queries which automatically receives the latest data of external scientific databases on a daily basis (SQL, SQL Dumps, REST, Bash Script, Linux)

INTERN & WORKING STUDENT 02/2017 - 08/2019

Edataconsulting GmbH

Heidelberg, Germany

- collaborated with an international team to research and prototype VR & AR applications
- developed an AR application which has been used on fairs and exhibitions to promote and showcase the company interactively (Unity, C#, Microsoft Hololens, Microsoft Kinect, Blender)

INTERN 05/2013 - 07/2013

Acteno Energy GmbH

Heidelberg, Germany

• improved data visualisation of the company's internal software which monitors power consumption of their clients (C#, ASP.NET, HTML, CSS)

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF MANNHEIM

02/2014 - 08/2019

B.Sc. in Computer Science

Thesis describes architecture for convolutional autoencoder to classify images on Raspberry Pi Zero

Mannheim, Germany

SRH TECHNICAL SCHOOL

TOOLS

10/2011 - 10/2013

Training in Computer Sciences for game- and multimedia development

Heidelberg, Germany

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE Experienced: Typescript/Javascript, Python, Java, C#, CSS/Sass, HTML, SQL

Familiar: Bash Scripting | GraphQL

LIBRARIES & FRAMEWORKS ReactJS, MobX, Redux, Tailwind CSS, Framer Motion, Numpy, Matplotlib, Kivy, Tkinter

Git | Linux | REST | VSCode | Docker | Unity | Blender | Photoshop

LANGUAGES Native: German | Fluent: English